《超女》前情提要
Previously on Supergirl...
是我干的
It was me.
我把我弟弟从我们的脑海中删去了
I erased my own brother from our minds.
你骗了我
You lied.
我认为关于杰罗德的报道你知道内幕
I think you know more about the Jarrod story
出于某些原因  你不想让我报道
and for some reason you don't want me on it.
你让我
You asked me
在你面前完全做我自己
to be completely myself with you.
我只能百分百运行
I can only operate at 100%.
我弟弟现在有了植入能力
My brother now has the power to incept.
让你违背自己的意愿听从他的指令
Make you do the things he wants you to do against your will.
Q波在凯莉和马拉法克的思维中
The Q-waves somehow forged a link
建立了一种联系
between Kelly's mind and Malefic's.
即使在他变身时  她也能看见他
She could see him, even when he shapeshifted.
我们要把凯莉送到安全的地方
We need to get Kelly to safety.
你今晚就走
You should leave tonight.
拿着
Take this.
这是莱克斯的物质传送门手表
It's one of Lex's transmatter portal watches.
如果有麻烦  直接用
If you need it, use it.
你跑不掉了  人类
You cannot run, human.
我不是人类  弟弟
I'm no human, brother.
安静的和我来
我保证不会再让任何人伤害你
你懂什么伤痛
What do you know of hurt?
当你所爱之人背叛你
When the ones you love turn their back on you,
那才是痛  你会尝到的
that's pain. But you'll see,
我要让你尝到你让我所承受的痛苦
when you suffer the way you made me suffer.
你没法在不伤害自己的情况下碰到我
You can't touch me without hurting yourself.
所以他才带我来了
That's why he brought me.
我们有备而来
We came prepared.
你现在无法用植入能力影响我们
You can't incept any of us now.
别那么肯定
Don't be so sure.
布莱克特工
Agent Blake?
荣恩  现在
J'onn, now.
超 女
第五季 第四集
你还好吗
Hey, you okay?
-挺好  -我们马上到范阿姨那了
- Yeah. - We'll be at Aunt Vi's in a few.
你知道  在爸爸死后来这里
You know, coming here after dad died,
拯救了我
that's what saved me.
我不知道如果当初范阿姨
I don't know what would've happened
没有收留我们会发生什么
if Aunt Vi hadn't taken us in.
我知道
I know.
加尔文镇欢迎你
我的天啊  这地方怎么这样了
My God, what happened to this place?
那是监狱吗
Is that a prison?
那绝对是新建的
That's definitely new.
请向前站
Step forward, please.
眼睛向前看
Eyes straight ahead.
火星人应对方案已经进行了
The Martian protocol is in place.
最起码马拉法克进不来了
At least Malefic won't get in here.
布莱尼
Hey, Brainy.
刚才是怎么回事
What the hell happened?
马拉法克不应该能够穿过
Malefic should have not been able to phase through
幻影区投影仪的
the Phantom Zone projector.
还有我们的精神力抑制器  被他烧毁了
And our psychic inhibitors, he fried them.
马拉法克的大脑和其它绿火星人都不同
Malefic's brain is unlike any other Green Martian.
我试着匹对它特殊的生理构造  但是...
I tried to calibrate both to his unique physiology, but--
那是我们唯一能够骗到他的机会
That was our one shot at tricking him.
他现在可能去找凯莉了  我的凯莉
He could be after the real Kelly, my Kelly right now.
我们不会让他得逞的
We are not gonna let that happen.
肯定还有别的办法能让我们追踪他
There's gotta be another way we can track him.
我们忽视了什么
Something we're missing.
他冲你喊了什么  辛达尔克吗
What did he yell at you, J'onn? Synd'ar'k?
我不知道
Uh, I don't know.
是个我没听过的土语
It's, um, it's a dialect I've not heard before.
我们不能再犯任何错了
We can't afford any more missteps.
我让人把维达克冲击枪从军火库里拿出来了
I'm having the Verdex Blaster brought up from the armory.
-什么  -艾丽克斯
- What? - Alex.
维达克冲击枪是汉克·亨肖设计用来
That Verdex Blaster was designed by Hank Henshaw
杀死绿色火星人的  尤其是我
to kill Green Martians, specifically me.
是最后手段
It's a last resort.
汉克·亨肖看错你了
Hank Henshaw was wrong about you,
但是马拉法克却是那种
but Malefic is exactly the kind of Martian
这冲击枪所针对的火星人
that this blaster was designed for.
等下  等等  咱们别着急做决定
Hang on, wait, wait, wait. Let's not rush into this.
因为如果我们拿了维达克冲击枪
Because if we had had the Verdex Blaster,
马拉法克可能会控制我们中一人来攻击荣恩
Malefic could've incepted one of us to use it on J'onn.
至少先让布莱尼修好这个
Let's at least have Brainy try to fix it first.
好吧
Okay.
好
很好  我会调整
Excellent. I shall adjust
幻影地带投射器的波长
the Phantom Zone projector's wavelengths
阻止马拉法克穿过
so Malefic cannot phase through it
然后同事
while simultaneously
重新校准精神力抑制器的频率
recalibrating the psychic inhibitor frequencies
以此来转移我受伤之心的注意力
all to distract myself from my broken heart.
-什么  -什么
- Uh, what? - What?
没什么  怎么了
Nothing. Why?
你听说什么了吗
What did you hear?
或许我们改叫莉娜来帮忙
Maybe we should call in Lena for backup.
尼娅  怎么了
Nia, what's up?
我在调查威廉的背景
I was doing some background on William,
猜猜嫁给成功律师这事上谁撒谎了  他
and guess whose marriage to a successful lawyer is a lie? His.
你知道他放在桌子上那张他妻子的照片吗
You know that picture of his wife he keeps on his desk?
是他从网上下载的套图
It's a stock photo he got off the web.
还有安德里亚同意让他在伦敦写的那篇文章
And that article Andrea cleared him to write from London?
我对那事有种奇怪的预感
Well, I had a weird feeling about it.
所以我用星体投射跟踪了他
So I astral projected and I followed him,
那简直就像是007电影里的情节
it was like something out of a James Bond movie.
他收到了一个人给的报纸
He got passed this newspaper from some guy,
然后他就突然不去伦敦了
and now, all of a sudden, he's no longer going to London,
埃琳娜·托雷斯
安德雷斯·贝略 426 波朗科区
墨西哥城  上午10点
他要去墨西哥城了
he's going to Mexico City.
-这个人是谁  -我们看看
- Who is this guy? - Well, let's see,
他是个充满神秘的骗子
he's a liar who is literally made of shadows,
现在他要去南方见一个名叫
and now he's going south to meet someone named
埃琳娜·托雷斯的人
Elena Torres.
我想她可能是他的下一个目标
I think she might be his next target.
干得好
Good work.
-是尼娅吗  -是的
- It was Nia? - Yes.
是的  她有了威廉姆的新线索
Yes, she has another lead on William.
另一起可能的暗杀尝试
Another possible assassination attempt.
如果你认为某人生命有危险
Well, if you think someone's life is at stake,
-那你就该出动了  -你确定吗
- then you should go. - Are you sure?
-凯莉的事  -我确定
- With Kelly? - I'm sure.
好吧
Okay.
等下  在你走之前
Wait, before... Before you go.
尼娅有问到我吗
Did Nia ask about me?
-我的天  -我不是在乎
- Oh, God. - Not that I care.
我是说  我不是在乎  不是什么大事
I mean, not that I don't care, it's not a big deal.
我给莉娜打电话
I'll call Lena.
当然  艾丽克斯  我马上过去
Of course, Alex, I'll be right over.
我想我隔离出了问题  卢瑟小姐
I believe I've isolated the problem, Ms. Luthor.
莱克斯的日记帮助我们造出了植入调节器
Lex's journals helped us build the inception tuner
可以给大脑植入想法
to implement thoughts into the brain,
但是特殊的Q波频率不正确
but the specific Q-wave frequency is incorrect.
不幸的是
Unfortunately,
这让我们需要尝试成百上千种变量
that leaves us with hundreds of thousands of variables.
我或许有个能加快进程的办法  霍普
I may have an expedited solution, Hope.
艾丽克斯刚请我帮助超查部
Alex has just asked me to assist the DEO
逮捕反叛的绿火星人
in apprehending a rogue Green Martian.
荣恩·荣兹的弟弟吗
The brother of J'onn J'onzz?
是的
Yes.
显然  他有能力
Apparently, he has the ability to override
重改他人的想法
another person's thoughts with his own.
从而控制思想
Mind control.
使用Q波
Using Q-waves.
如果能收获马拉法克的能力
If we were able to harness Malefic's abilities,
我们就能测量所需要的频率
we could use them to determine what frequency is needed
在脑海中植入想法
to implant thoughts into the brain.
研究和测试需要我们抓住研究对象
The study and testing would require us to detain the subject.
我觉得超女和她朋友们不会赞成
I doubt Supergirl or her friends would approve.
不
No.
我觉得他们会
I don't think they would.
至少范阿姨的房子没变
At least Aunt Vi's house hasn't changed.
-是马拉法克吗  -在这等着
- Malefic? -Wait here.
我看到一些孩子跑到树林里了
I saw some kids running into the woods.
他们是来偷东西的吗
Were they stealing stuff?
我想他们只是在做作业
I think they were doing homework.
墨西哥城
打扰一下
我在找埃琳娜·托雷斯
我很遗憾  小姐
谢谢
为什么有人想杀她
Why would anyone want to kill her?
她是黑曜石之北公司的首席会计师
She was the lead accountant for Obsidian Worldwide.
也就是我们的母公司
You mean, our parent company?
也是威廉的
And William's.
还有  我追踪了你发给我的车牌号
Also, I tracked that license plate number you sent me
我们在纳市警局的朋友有回复了
and got a hit back courtesy of our friends at the NCPD.
这是塞尔吉奥·拉莫斯
Meet Sergio Ramos,
墨西哥城有名的帮派成员
known player in Intergang, Mexico City.
你是说威廉与集团犯罪有牵连吗
Are you saying that William is involved with organized crime?
开始听起来像国际刺客了
This is starting to get a little international assassin-y.
我们需要证据
We need proof.
我们必须找出他有她什么把柄
We have to find out what he had on her.
她又有他什么把柄
What she had on him.
我想再次提醒你
I want to remind you again.
这很可能会相当痛苦
This is liable to be quite painful.
我们要校准幻影地带投射器
Until we calibrate the Phantom Zone projector
以锁定火星能量特征
to lock onto a Martian energy signature,
确保无论能量的密度多大
regardless of the Martian's density,
那股火星能量都无法穿透它
so they can't phase through it.
我准备好了
I'm ready when you are.
初始相位为25%
Commencing phasing at 25%.
糟糕  糟糕  糟糕
Sprock, sprock, sprock.
我没事  我没事
I'm okay. I'm okay.
哪里出了错
What went wrong?
太过头了  太过头了
It was too much, too much, too much...
精神力抑制器的加强就快完成了
I'm almost done reinforcing the psychic inhibitors,
如果你需要的话我可以帮你
so I can help you, if you want it.
我听到惨叫声了  出什么事了
I heard the scream. What happened?
-怎么做  怎么做  -布莱尼
- How, how... - Brainy?
我会  我会解决的  好吗
Yeah, I'm... I'll figure it out, all right?
我会解决一切的
I'll figure it all out.
抱歉  荣恩  但我们需要做好万全准备
I'm sorry, J'onn, we need all of our options on the table.
我要去准备冲击枪
I'm prepping the blaster.
艾丽克斯
Alex.
艾丽克斯  请不要这样
Alex, please don't.
我无法
I don't...
我无法理解你为什么要维护他
I don't understand why you are defending him.
他在战时背叛了你和所有绿火星人
He betrayed you and all of the Green Martians during the war.
因为他  他们惨遭屠杀
They were slaughtered because of him.
我只是因为他的行为充满愧疚
I'm just really sorry he's doing this.
你没有理由感到愧疚
Well, you have nothing to be sorry about.
明白吗  这不是你的错
Okay? This isn't your fault.
是我的错
It's mine.
凯莉身处险境都是因为我和我的工作
It is killing me that Kelly is in danger
这让我无比煎熬  我很怕
because of me and my job, and I am terrified
怕他会想办法利用我来伤害她
that he is going to use me somehow to get to her,
我只能不停祈祷她平安无事
and I just keep praying that she's safe.
我永远不会让她受到伤害
I would never let anything happen to her.
这是你无法保证的
You can't promise that.
我知道你是想安慰我  我知道
I know that you are trying to make me feel better, I do.
但只有那个怪物被解决  我才会感到安慰
But I won't, not until that monster is taken care of.
你去做能让你感到安全的事
You do what you need to do to feel safe.
但我不会放弃布莱尼
But I'm not giving up on Brainy.
这里变了好多
So much around here has changed.
至少有一件事变得更好了
Oh, at least one thing has changed for the better.
纳尔逊·斯图尔特
Nelson Stewart?
你不是曾为这个记者做过实习生吗
Isn't that the reporter you interned for?
纳尔逊教会了我关于新闻诚信的一切
Nelson taught me everything I know about journalistic integrity.
监狱职务促进当地经济
出版商  做得好  纳尔逊
Publisher? Yeah, way to go, Nelson.
这太棒了
That's what I'm talking about.
够了  我要报警
That's it, I'm calling the cops.
-我准备付钱的  -你放开他
- I'm gonna pay for it. - Hey, get your hands off of him.
-他在偷东西  -这是什么道理
- He was stealing. - Last time I checked,
人还没离开商店怎么能算偷东西
it wasn't stealing when you're still in the store.
再说  是我叫他帮我买的
And besides, I asked him to get it for me.
我来付款
I'm paying for it.
把意饺还给他
Now give him back the ravioli.
多谢  女士
Thanks a lot, lady.
我见过你  对吗  你就是之前
I met you, right? You're one of the kids
房子里那些孩子之一
from before from the house.
那又如何
Uh, yeah, so?
那  你叫什么名字
So, you have a name?
西蒙·柯比
Simon Kirby.
很高兴认识你  西蒙  我是凯莉
It's nice to meet you, Simon. I'm Kelly.
-我是詹姆斯  -我知道你是谁
- I'm James. - I know who you are.
我也看新闻  凯特科  守护者
I read the news, CatCo. Guardian. Duh.
吃的还给你
Uh, here's your food back.
-我先失陪  -好
- I'm gonna... - Yeah.
我妹妹今晚想亲自下厨做晚餐
So, my sister's planning a homemade dinner tonight.
她厨艺很差
She's an awful cook.
你要是能过来陪我们一起吃饭
You know, you'd be doing me a solid
会帮我个大忙
if you came by and ate with us.
我闯进你家
I broke into your house,
在你的客厅过夜
camped out in your living room,
我的弥补方式就是去做客吃难吃的晚餐吗
and I can make it up to you by coming over and eating bad food?
是的  所谓祸不单行
Yeah. Misery loves company.
那么
So...
你来吗
What do you say?
埃琳娜·托雷斯公寓
你好  有人在吗
抱歉  门没锁  你是埃琳娜·托雷斯吗
Sorry. It was open. Elena Torres?
这不是私人恩怨
Don't take this personally.
你可能会给那位女士造成重伤
Hey, you really could've hurt that lady.
超女
Supergirl?
我很好奇
I wonder,
你需要呼吸吗
do you need to breathe?
艾丽克斯
Alex?
斯隆特工
Agent Sloan,
超女带了一名犯人回来
Supergirl's bringing a prisoner in,
-准备一间牢房  -好的  长官
- prep a cell. - Yes, ma'am.
马拉法克
Malefic.
你植入了有权限接触火星协议的人
You incepted someone to bypass the Martian protocol.
-放下枪  -你先放
- Put your gun down. - You first.
这就好多了
That's better.
现在我哥哥的朋友成了他的敌人
Now my brother's friend is his enemy.
我试过审问她关于威廉的事
I tried grilling her about William,
但她不肯开口
but she's not talking.
马拉法克有什么新消息吗
Any news on Malefic?
还没有
Nothing yet.
你确定你没事吗
You sure you're okay?
没事  谢了
I am, yeah, thanks.
你该了解一下我哥哥的罪行了
Now it's time you learned my brother's crimes.
披萨很快就烤好了
Pizza will be ready in a few.
你人真好  帮助了我
That was so cool, what you did for me
在商店时
at the store.
人人都会那样做的
Anyone would've done the same.
不  没有人会那样做
No, nobody would've done it.
在这里没有人会为其他人冒险
Nobody risks their neck for anybody around here.
但你帮了  又厉害又无私
But you did. It was badass and selfless.
那样冒烟是正常的嘛
Is it supposed to do that?
-你还好吗  -出什么事了
- You okay? - What happened?
没事  我只是头疼
Nothing, I just... headache.
我要出去透透气  你能看着披萨吗
Um, I'm gonna get some air, will you watch the pizza?
当然
Yeah, of course.
好
Okay.
感觉还行
Oh, it's not that bad.
我喜欢吃焦的
I like it burned.
那好极了
Good thing.
你在我姨妈家住了多久
So how long you been living in my aunt's house?
几个月
Couple of months.
有时我们去朋友家住
Sometimes we crash with friends,
有时就在深林里露宿
sometimes we just camp out in the woods.
你爸妈呢
Where are your parents?
从五岁起  就没见过我
Haven't seen my dad since I was...
爸爸
five?
我妈妈去年冬天被警察抓走了
My mom got busted last winter
因为从五金店偷取暖器
stealing a space heater from the hardware store.
法官连解释的机会都不给她
The judge wouldn't even give her a chance to explain.
因为偷30块的取暖器  她被判十年监禁
They gave her 10 years for stealing a 30 buck heater.
什么时候起小偷小摸判这么长时间了
Since when does petty theft get you that kind of time?
警察  法官和律师都是串通好的
It's a racket. The cops, judges, lawyers,
包括所有参与的人
everyone's in on it.
他们要让监狱人满为患
They keep the prison full,
因为监狱能让他们腰缠万贯
the prison keeps their pockets lined.
怎么会没人站出来反抗他们
How's nobody stood up against them?
举报他们
Called these guys out?
比如说谁
Like who?
没人会以身犯险举报他们
Nobody's gonna speak up and risk themselves.
反正没人能打破这个体制  又何必徒劳
Anyways, you can't beat the system, so what's the point?
并不是徒劳的  西蒙
There is a point, Simon.
你必须站出来  对抗不公之事
You have to stand up and fight against injustice.
每个人都只为自己着想
Everyone's just out for their own skin.
世界就是这样的
It's the way it is.
在我的看管下就不会
Not on my watch.
该死
Sprock.
我好像不仅没让光束变弱   反而更强了
I seem to have made the beam more dense instead of less.
再试一次
Let's go again.
让我休息会
Just give me a minute.
荣恩  你不能让自己
Okay, J'onn, you can't keep putting yourself
反复经受这种惩罚
through this punishment.
-我没事  -不
- I'm fine. - No.
不  你都快站不起来了
You're not, you can barely stand.
找到你弟弟时  你得力量充沛对付他
And we need you at full strength for when we find your brother.
我和你说过
I told you.
我会帮布莱尼的
I will help Brainy,
这样艾丽克斯就不必用喷枪了
so Alex doesn't have to use the blaster.
清醒一下头脑
Go clear your head.
布莱尼  我知道你没叫我帮忙
Look, Brainy, I know you haven't asked for help,
-但我肯定会帮你的  -不
- but you're getting it anyway. - No.
我要全神贯注去解决这个问题
I need my mind consumed with this problem,
这样我就不会想尼娅了
so I don't think of Nia.
你的小盒子怎么了
What happened to your little boxes?
小盒子让我无法拥有一段真正的感情
Little boxes prevented me from having a real relationship.
可惜  脱离小盒子的我
Unfortunately, my unboxed self
无法成为一个好男友
does not make a particularly good boyfriend.
所以我这几天一直在审视自己
So I have been analyzing myself for days,
为我心爱的女人寻找自我调节的方法
searching for a way to modulate myself for the woman I love.
我不会给你感情方面的建议
Well, I'm not gonna give you relationship advice.
但作为科学家  你似乎陷入了一个无限循环
But as a scientist, you seem to be stuck in an infinite loop,
除非你能跳出循环  否则你会崩溃的
and unless you can escape, you're headed for a crash.
-那样就会变成灾难了  -改变一个变量
- That would be cataclysmic. - So change a variable.
还有哪件事你没尝试过
What's the one thing you haven't tried yet?
找人帮忙呢
Asking for help?
你会...
Will you he...
你会帮
Will you help...
我吗
me?
当然
Yes.
我想小小的改变能大大地帮助你和尼娅
And I think a small dose of that will go a long way with Nia.
帮我找个极性调节器  我们开工吧
Okay, could you find me a polarity tuner, and we can get to work?
加尔文镇公报
谁给我找个摄影师
Somebody get me a photographer,
这里有名人出现
we got a celebrity sighting here.
纳尔逊  怎么样  兄弟  你好吗
Nelson, what's up, brother, how you doing?
吉米·奥尔森
Jimmy Olsen.
你怎么来了
What the hell are you doing here?
希望你不是来找工作的
I hope you're not looking for a job,
我们可请不起你
we can't afford you.
不  其实我有新闻要告诉你
No, I've actually come with a story.
我在这遇到一个小孩
So I met this local kid
他说他妈妈因小偷小摸被判入狱十年
who says his mom is serving 10 years for petty theft?
所以我查了一下  你后院那座监狱
So I did some digging, and that prison in your backyard
似乎有很多人因为小罪
seems to have a lot of people serving long sentences
而被判长期徒刑
for small crimes.
是的  看来有的人运气不好
Yeah, people have bad luck, I guess.
运气不好
Bad luck?
你不觉得这是监狱腐败的问题吧
It's prison corruption, wouldn't you say?
很难说清楚
It's, um, it's complicated.
但愿我能帮到你  可是...
Look, I wish I could help you, but--
你可以帮我  纳尔逊  所以我才来
You can help me, Nelson, that's why I'm here.
新闻业旨在为小市民打抱不平
Journalism's about fighting for the little guy,
这是你教我的
you taught me that.
你的工作旨在找出腐败现象
It's your job to point out corruption,
这里到底是怎么了
so what the hell's going on here?
有些人的情况已经改变了
Things have changed for some people.
理想主义无法养家糊口
Idealism doesn't feed a family.
媒体的力量
And this whole power of the press thing,
有媒体集团和那位斗篷女孩的支持
it might work if you've got the backing of a media conglomerate
才可能有点用处
and a certain girl with a cape.
但在这里毫无意义可言
But around here, it doesn't mean anything.
坚持正义总是有意义的
Standing up for what's right always means something.
纳尔逊
Nelson.
那座监狱正在践踏整个小镇
That prison is stomping on the neck of this entire town.
但那也是唯一延续这座小镇的东西
It's also the only thing that's keeping this town alive.
我很乐意看到这些混蛋受到惩罚
Look, I'd love to see these bastards get what they deserve.
但如果我爆出他们的内幕
But if I call them out,
我的广告商就会撤资
my advertisers, they pull their money,
丢饭碗的不止我一个人
not only am I out of a job
还有我雇佣的30个人
but so are the 30 other people I employ.
回纳欣诺市吧
Go back to National City.
我希望你待在那里
I like to think of you there.
我只是很高兴有人能逃离这个小镇
You know, I'm just glad somebody made it out of this town.
很高兴逃离的人是你
And I'm glad it was you.
听听  我在《墨西哥城先驱报》的线人说
Listen to this. So my contact at the Mexico City Herald
停尸房有异样
said the morgue had a discrepancy.
埃琳娜的尸体被烧得面目全非
Elena's body was burned beyond recognition,
但是可以用门牙来确认身份
but they were able to use an incisor to confirm ID and...
不是她
it wasn't a match.
显然  他们从车里拉出来的尸体
Apparently, the body they pulled from the car
已经死了两周  是自然死亡
had been dead for two weeks and died of natural causes.
所以他们伪造了埃琳娜的死吗
So they faked Elena's death?
这倒是让我对我的消息有了新的见解
Well, that sheds new light on my news.
我让我的会计朋友查过你在埃琳娜公寓里
I ran the numbers you found at Elena's apartment
找到的账号
by my accountant friend,
结果发现和一个离岸账户有关
and it turns out it's linked to an offshore bank account.
去年一直有人往账户转账
Someone's been funneling money into it for the past year,
账本上有两个人的名字
and there are two names listed on the ledger,
一个是埃琳娜  另一个是匿名
one is Elena's and the other is anonymous.
-你觉得是威廉吗  -有可能
- You think William? - Maybe.
难道是挪用公款吗
Embezzlement, is that what this is?
我朋友说账户上有一个地址
My friend says there's an address listed to the account,
但地址是加密的
but it's encrypted.
打给布莱尼  看看他能否解开
Let's call Brainy, see if he can crack it.
或者我可以叫我朋友去弄
Or I could ask my friend to do it.
你们俩还有隔阂吗
Are things still weird between you guys?
他今早是有点心不在焉
He did seem a little off this morning.
我就怕事情会变成这样
I was afraid this would happen.
我想如果我能跟布莱尼坦白
I thought that if I was just honest with Brainy,
也许能解决我们的问题
it would help solve our problems,
可却让事情恶化了
but it's only made things worse.
我知道我们可以一起解决这个问题
I know it's something that we could work through together,
但他觉得这是他该解决的问题
but he thinks that it's his problem to solve,
现在都不肯跟我说话
and now he won't even talk to me.
你也了解布莱尼
Well, you know how Brainy is,
有时候人的情感会吓到他
sometimes human emotions just throw him for a loop.
他应该只是需要时间
I think he just needs time,
到时候就意识到你不会离开他了
and to realize you're not going anywhere.
好  那你把这个拿给你朋友
Okay. So you get this back to your friend,
看看他能不能去掉加密
see if she can unencrypt it.
我要去超查部
I'm gonna get to the DEO.
跟艾丽克斯和荣恩谈谈
Talk to Alex and J'onn,
看看有没有马拉法克的消息
see if there's any news on the Malefic front.
收到  上司
Copy that, boss.
我们就快成功了  我有预感
We are so close to cracking this, I can feel it.
天晴的日子  在这就能看见火星的卫星
On a clear day, you can see the moons of Mars from here.
今天不是晴天
Today's not a clear day.
我知道你做的事了  荣恩
I found out what you've done, J'onn.
你骗了我们所有人
You lied to all of us.
你将我们置于危险之中
You put us in jeopardy,
以保护你自己
so that you could protect yourself.
保护你的秘密
Keep your secret safe.
你抹去了你亲生弟弟的存在
That you mind-wiped the existence of your own brother--
艾丽克斯  我本想告诉你的
Alex, I wanted to tell you,
但我感觉很羞耻
but I was so ashamed.
我向你袒露
I confided in you
这一切对我的折磨
how this was tearing me apart.
对你说  我让凯莉身处险境
How I thought that I was the one putting Kelly in danger,
而你却无动于衷
and you just stood there,
明明知道这不是我的错
knowing that it wasn't my fault.
而是你的错
That it was yours.
你让我以为马拉法克才是那个魔鬼
You had me convinced that Malefic was the monster,
但他不单单是追杀人的魔鬼
but he wasn't just some bad guy coming after people.
他是你创造的魔鬼
He was some bad guy that you created
追杀你的亲人
coming after your family, and again
而你只是袖手旁观
you just stood there,
你让我们承担后果
and you let us suffer the consequences.
-我知道  -你会说
- I know. - You may say
你抹去马拉法克的存在是为了保护家人
that you erased Malefic to protect your family,
保护梅林
to protect Myr'nn.
还是说你这么做是因为
Or you did it because it was easier
-这比帮助他更简单  -不
- than helping him. - No.
不  不
No, no.
马拉法克不是魔鬼  荣恩
Malefic isn't the monster here, J'onn.
你才是
You are.
艾丽克斯
Alex.
好  谢谢
Yeah, okay, thanks.
那个
Hey, so...
报纸的事虽然没戏了  但是
The newspaper might've been a bust, but good news,
纳欣诺市最好的律师
the best lawyer in National City
决定接下你母亲的案子
has decided to take your mom's case.
真的吗
For real?
真的  我不会开这种玩笑的
Yeah, I wouldn't kid about that.
别担心律师费
And don't worry about her fee.
我来付
I'll cover it.
我们什么时候见她
When do we meet her?
我可以安排你们下周见面
I could probably set up a meeting with you guys next week.
你不去吗
You mean, you won't be there?
不不不  我...
Oh, no, no, I...
我只是回来看看  西蒙  不能久留
This was a visit, Simon, I can't stay here.
好吧
Right.
当然了  怎么可能呢
Of course, why would you?
这镇子就是个破地方
This town is a hellhole.
不不不  不是这样的
Hey, no, no, it's not like that.
没关系
It's cool.
我明白
I get it.
不是你的问题
It's not your problem.
感谢帮忙  也谢谢你留我吃饭
Thanks for the help and the food.
再见
See you around.
西蒙
Simon.
荣恩
J'onn?
怎么了
What is it?
是马拉法克的事吗
Is it something about Malefic?
辛达尔克
Synd'ar'k.
辛达尔克是罪人的意思  马拉法克朝我喊的
A synd'ar'k is a sinner, that's what Malefic yelled at me.
我请尼娅用梦境能力
I asked Nia to use her dream power
帮我查出我弟弟
to help me find the truth about my brother,
记忆抹除的真相
about the mind wipe.
我们发现...
That's when we discovered...
我弟弟并非生来邪恶
My brother wasn't born evil.
他有障碍
He had a problem.
我们
And we...
排挤他
ostracized him.
我把马拉法克从我们的记忆中抹除了
I wiped Malefic's existence from our minds.
是我
It was me.
是我干的
I did this.
我一次又一次地让族人失望
I failed my people more than once.
我让你们失望
I'm failing you.
不  不  你救了我们无数次
No, no, you've saved us countless times.
去年氪石散布于地球
I would've been dead last year,
要不是你  我就没命了
when the Earth was seeded with Kryptonite, if it weren't for you.
但是
Still...
把他从我们的记忆中抹除
Wiping him from our mind?
就像杀害自己的兄弟一样
It's like I murdered my own brother.
但你现在回忆起来了
But you remember now.
你冒着生命危险
You risked your own life
去寻找记忆  现在你可以找回他
to find those memories, and now you can find him
做出不同的选择
and make different choices.
我太自私了
It was so selfish of me to...
让尼娅替我保守秘密
burden Nia with my secret,
不告诉你和艾丽克斯
and keep this from you and Alex.
幸好尼娅告诉她了
But I'm glad Nia told her.
她应该知道真相  你也是
She deserves to know the truth, and so do you.
不可能是尼娅说的  她跟我在一起
It couldn't have been Nia, she's been with me.
是马拉法克
That was Malefic.
他植入了艾丽克斯
He incepted Alex.
我找不到艾丽克斯
I can't find Alex anywhere.
她关了手机和对讲机
She turned off her phone and her comms.
幻影区投射器和精神力抑制器
Where are we with the Phantom Zone projector
怎么样了
and psychic inhibitors?
重新安装校准过了
Reconfigured and recalibrated.
超女  维达克冲击枪不见了
Supergirl, the Verdex Blaster is missing
军火库里对抗火星人的火炮不见了
and the armory's cleared out of anti-Martian artillery.
-全部消失了  -我们必须马上找到艾丽克斯
- It's all gone. - We have to find Alex now.
有办法了
There is a way.
我可以试试通过精神交流找到她
I could try and find her psychically.
马拉法克的心灵对所有绿火星人有毒
Malefic's mind is poisonous to all Green Martians.
你和艾丽克斯被植入过的心灵融合
Melding with Alex's incepted mind
马拉法克就能进入你的心灵
would allow Malefic into yours.
你会受伤
It could hurt you.
重要的是找到艾丽克斯
All that matters is finding Alex.
艾丽克斯
Alex.
向我敞开你的心灵
Open your mind for me.
我们在找你
We are looking for you.
我们要让你回家
We need you to come home.
求求你  艾丽克斯  回答我
Please, Alex, answer me.
你已经尽力了  詹姆斯
You did what you could for him, James.
还不够
It wasn't enough.
虽然西蒙说
I mean, when Simon says
这不是我的问题  但它应该是
it's not my problem, maybe it should be.
这孩子身边没有别人了
I mean, this kid's got nobody.
你还好吗
Hey, you okay?
我看到
I'm having...
一些画面
visions.
我以为他们进入了我的思想
I thought they were in my head,
但自从黑曜石那事之后
but whatever happened at Obsidian,
我不止能看见马拉法克
it didn't just allow me to see Malefic.
我好像跟他相通
I think I'm connected to him.
我能看见他的视野
I think I can see what he sees.
艾丽克斯在他手上  我们得回纳欣诺市
And he has Alex. We need to go back to National City now.
我们不能回纳欣诺市
We're not going back to National City.
我们过来就是为了带你远离马拉法克
We came here to get you away from Malefic.
詹姆斯  你穿上守护者战衣时
James, when you put on that Guardian suit,
你会先考虑好吗
do you think first?
还是看到有人需要帮助就采取行动
Or do you see someone in trouble and act?
-这不一样  -怎么不一样
- That's different. - The hell it is.
马上回去
We're going back now.
该死的  马拉法克  她在哪里
Damn it, Malefic, where is she?
荣恩
J'onn.
我在天文馆等你
Meet me at the planetarium.
一个人来
Come alone.
欢迎来到火星
Welcome to Mars,
这里曾经生活着伟大的文明
home to a once great civlization.
后来因火星大内战而灭绝
Wiped out by the Great Martian civil war.
一位绿火星人如今生活在地球
One Green Martian now lives on Earth among us.
火星猎人
The Martian Manhunter.
这个懦夫
A coward
让他的家族独自面对死亡和绝望
who left his family to face an agonizing death and worse.
而他来了这里  为此作偿
And he's come here to pay for it.
艾丽克斯  不要
Alex, please.
艾丽克斯
Alex.
我知道是我弟弟在逼你这样做
I know my brother's making you do this.
如果你能听到我说话  他也可以
And if you can hear me, so can he.
我不该赶你走的
I never should have banished you.
我现在知道了
I know that now.
我在地球上活了三百多年
I've lived on Earth for over 300 years.
但我从未有一天获得过安宁
But I never really found true peace.
我认为这是因为我对你做的事  马拉法克
And I believe it's because of what I did to you, Malefic.
你没有背叛我们
You didn't betray us.
我们与白火星人结盟
By aligning with the White Martians,
是我们背叛了你
we betrayed you.
我们想治好你
We tried to fix you.
改变你
Change you.
但我们最应该做的  就是接受你
When all along, we should've accepted you.
我现在接受你了  弟弟
I accept you now, brother.
-不  -是的
- No! - Yes.
你逼我自我审视
You forced me to look inside myself
发现了我删除的记忆
and discover memories I had erased.
你这样做是为了惩罚我
You did it to try and punish me.
但是
But...
你不觉得这是我们的第二次机会吗
Don't you see you've given us a second chance?
我们现在还来得及  弟弟
It's not too late for us, brother.
我们...
It's not...
还...
too...
来得及
late.
我的天哪
Oh, my God.
我做了什么
What have I done?
不
No!
在火星  你对我只有残忍
On Mars, you had nothing but cruelty for me.
这份爱和原谅是哪里来的
Where did this love and forgiveness come from?
是我家人教我的
From my family.
家人会毁掉你
Family's supposed to destroy you.
他本应自己来
He was supposed to come alone too.
到此为止了  马拉法克
This ends now, Malefic.
你跟我的朋友们说吧
Tell that to my friends.
他们被植入了
They've been incepted.
护盾矩阵  荣恩
The shield matrix, J'onn.
这么强的火力  穹顶撑不住的
Yeah, this dome won't last with all the firepower.
那是什么
What is that?
我们不会再次失去你了
We are not going to lose you again.
屋顶
The roof.
如果塌了  这里的人都会死
If it collapses, then everyone in here is gonna die.
走吧  卡拉  快走
Go. Kara, go.
荣恩  你帮我解开
J'onn, you gotta get me out of this thing.
凯莉  你不应该来这里
Kelly, you shouldn't be here.
这就是我应该在的地方
This is exactly where I should be here.
-那到底是个什么东西  -天哪
- What the hell is that thing? - Oh, my God.
是炸弹  是塔玛拉星和法罗依德技术的结合
A bomb. A hybrid of Tamaranean and Pharoid technology.
与艾丽克斯的分子结构同步了
It's synched to Alex's molecular structure.
超女  听得到吗
Supergirl, can you hear me?
可以
Yeah.
穹顶落下之后  你和守护者
When the dome fails, you and Guardian
收回所有被偷的武器
gather all of the stolen weapons.
凯莉  只有你能看到他  去找到马拉法克
Kelly, you're the only one who can see him, so find Malefic.
-荣恩  -你相信我吗
- J'onn. - Do you trust me?
相信
Yes.
超女  行动
Supergirl, now.
穿蓝色外套的就是马拉法克
It's Malefic in the blue jacket.
马拉法克回到幻影区了吗
So Malefic's back in the Phantom Zone?
抱歉你没能救他
I'm sorry that you couldn't save him.
荣恩  我知道你想救他
J'onn, I know that that's what you wanted to do.
但是你说的话我都听到了
But I heard everything that you said to him.
只是希望他能听进去
I just wish he could've taken it in.
但是既然我恢复了记忆
But maybe now that I remember,
也许总有一天我能够修复裂痕
I have a chance to make things right at some point.
你怎么能认为我会那样说你
How could you ever think that I would say those things
或者那样想你
or think those things about you?
可能是因为我那样想过我自己吧
I guess because I thought those things about myself.
我记得你曾经告诉过我
Well, I remember you telling me once that
艰难时刻才能看出真性格
true character reveals itself in times of hardship.
我现在知道你真正的样子了
And I know who you really are.
没有你  我们绝对做不到
We couldn't have done it without you.
别闹了  我基本什么都没做
Please, I barely did anything.
什么  抑制器和投射器都是你修好的
What? You fixed the inhibitors and the projector.
确实感觉不错
It did feel good.
我们两个作为搭档行动
You and me working together as a team.
我知道了你的真实身份
Now that I know who you actually are.
那就尽快习惯吧
Well, get used to it,
因为你现在已经是超女朋友了
because you are now officially a Superfriend.
我们有主题T恤  特定握手动作
We have T-shirts and a handshake.
回头教你  不复杂
I'll teach it to you. It's not a big deal.
有个流程
It's a whole thing.
我们今晚打算去喝酒  要来吗
We're going out to get drinks tonight, do you wanna come?
很想去  但是我已经在这里一天了
Oh, I would love to, but I have been here all day,
真得回L公司了
so I really should get back to L-Corp.
当然  拯救世界的天才全年无休
Of course. No rest for the world-saving genius.
既然马拉法克消失了
Since Malefic is gone,
不如少在前线战斗  多...
how about less fighting on the frontlines and more...
依偎着看看剧呢
cuddles and Netflix?
没问题
Okay, yeah, I'm in.
请接受我最诚挚的歉意
Please, take this as a token of my deepest apologies.
布莱尼  这个很好
Brainy, this is perfect.
我不知道我在何时
I do not know when or how
能够如何学会做自己
I will find a way to be myself,
而不是总被自己的强迫式性格左右
and yet not succumb to my more obsessive qualities.
也许我们可以一起努力
Perhaps we could work on it together?
我哪儿都不会去
I'm not going anywhere.
-快点  -好
- Hurry. Cause I... - Yeah.
总有人抢这个位置
People usually steal this.
我先
Dibs.
你刚才是说"我先"吗
Did you just say "Dibs"?
-是的  -干得漂亮
- I did. - Well done.
这杯敬我们一直在一起
Okay, here is to always being together.
干杯
Cheers.
说到这个
About that.
你们知道吧  我离开凯特科之后
You guys all know that I've been doing a lot of soul searching
一直在寻找自我
since I left CatCo.
想知道下一步该干什么
Trying to figure out what's next.
我知道我很想回馈  想帮助别人
I knew I wanted to give back, and I wanted to help people.
但是我快把自己逼疯了
But I was driving myself crazy trying to figure out
也没想出来该怎么努力
where to put those efforts.
直到我无比睿智的妹妹
And then my extremely wise sister...
给了我许多醍醐灌顶的建议
...gave me some damn good advice.
她说"别总想着把事情捋清楚
She said, "Stop trying so hard to figure things out,
你就静下来
and just be still
仔细听就好"
and listen."
于是我终于听到了
And finally I heard it.
但这声音并不是来自我的内心
Only it wasn't a voice from inside of me,
是一个孩子的声音
it was this kid's voice,
我们在加尔文镇遇见的一个孩子
this kid that we met in Calvintown.
可悲的是  那里成了犯罪和腐败的温床
Sadly, it's become this cesspool for crime and corruption.
他告诉我
And he told me that
没有人愿意帮忙
no one's there willing to help.
没有人愿意站起来做正确的事情
There's nobody willing to stand up and do the right thing.
没有人愿意冒生命危险
There's nobody willing to put their neck on the line.
就像那样
And just like that,
我知道我必须这么做
that's what I knew I had to do.
这么多年来  我一直作为守护者
Look, I've been fighting the good fight
在高级办公室里  在纳欣诺市街头
from a fancy corner office for years.
代表正义去战斗
And in the streets of National City as Guardian.
但我一开始只是一个拿着相机的男人
But I started off as a guy with a camera.
是我们爸爸给我的相机
A camera our dad gave me.
身处人群之中
Among the people.
那才是我该去的地方
And that is where I need to be.
目前
For now,
我要回加尔文镇
I'm going back to Calvintown.
我要回家
I'm going home.
我要让小镇的人知道
And I'm gonna show that town that there is somebody
有人愿意为他们而战
who is willing to fight for them.
我要买下加尔文镇公报
I'm gonna buy the Calvintown Gazette.
安德里亚·罗哈斯或许能阻止我
Look, Andrea Rojas may be able to stop me
为报纸写稿
from writing for a newspaper,
但她不能阻止我出版报纸
but she can't stop me from publishing one.
太棒了
That's amazing.
没有你我们该怎么办
And what are we gonna do without you?
我来纳欣诺市的一个主要原因
One of the main reasons I moved to National City
就是因为克拉克让我关照你
was because Clark wanted me to keep an eye on you.
但一直是你在关照我
But you're the one that kept an eye on me.
你从来都不需要我
You never needed me.
那时不需要  现在也不需要
Not then, and certainly not now.
但我们会想你的
Yeah, but we are going to miss you.
非常想
So much.
我的感情喷涌而出
My feelings are springing out,
我似乎找不到一个小盒子来装下它们
and I can't seem to find a little box to contain them.
好吧  试试这个盒子
Okay, try this box.
敬詹姆斯
To James.
不对
No.
敬你们大家
To you guys.
我无法相信詹姆斯真的离开了
I can't believe James is really gone.
我猜是我心中有一部分觉得他还会回来
I guess part of me always thought he'd come back.
我知道
I know.
但我为他感到高兴  这是他应得的
But I'm happy for him. He deserves this.
是的
Yeah.
卡拉
Kara?
怎么了
What is it?
我朋友破解了与埃琳娜账户关联的地址
My friend unencrypted the address associated with Elena's account.
就在这里
It's here.
在纳欣诺市
In National City.
什么
What?
你是怎么进来的
How the hell did you get in here?
-这是什么  -卡拉  离开这里
- What is this? - Kara, walk out of here,
忘掉你刚刚看见的
forget what you just saw.
-太危险了  -你是什么人
- It's too dangerous. - What are you?
-卧底警察吗  -我是个记者
- An undercover cop? - I'm a journalist,
跟你一样
like you.
我在伦敦为《泰晤士报》工作
I work for The Times in London,
我是来暗中调查安德里亚·罗哈斯
I'm here undercover to investigate Andrea Rojas.
我很抱歉  但你必须离开
I'm sorry, but you've got to leave.
在你搅入这件事之前
Before you get mixed up in this.
这次跟我说实话  也许我会离开
Be real with me this once, and maybe I will.
因为我已经知道你的离岸银行账户
'Cause I already know about your offshore bank account,
和埃琳娜·托雷共用的那个
the one you share with Elena Torres.
我知道你昨天在墨西哥城
I know you were in Mexico City yesterday,
帮她伪造自己的死亡
helping her fake her own death.
我知道你假装有个老婆  但你没有
I know that you pretend to have a wife, but you don't.
我知道杰罗德博士  斯特恩博士
I know about Dr. Jarrod, Dr. Stern,
所以你为什么不停止掩盖你的行踪
so why don't you stop trying to cover your tracks
而跟我实话实说呢
and just try telling the truth?
埃琳娜认为他们盯上了她
Elena thought they were onto her,
他们知道她在向别人透露信息
that they knew she was talking to someone,
我需要保她安全
I needed to keep her safe.
你的国际帮朋友塞尔吉奥·拉莫斯呢
And what about your Intergang friend Sergio Ramos?
塞尔吉奥是国际刑警  卧底
Sergio is Interpol, undercover.
他帮我带她离开
He helped me get her out.
如果罗哈斯家族有问题  你为什么不说
If the Rojases are dirty, why aren't you saying anything?
因为我还没有找到证据
Because I haven't found the proof yet.
两年的报道
Two years' worth of reporting
表明这是一个比阿尔·卡彭更大的犯罪阴谋
that suggests a criminal conspiracy bigger than Al Capone,
但没有任何证据直接指向罗哈斯家族
but nothing that connects the Rojases directly.
所以我才在凯特科工作  为了接近安德里亚
It's why I took the job at CatCo, to get close to Andrea.
尽我所能进入罗哈斯的小圈子
Doing everything I can to get into the Rojas inner circle.
自从你来到这里  就一直是个讨厌鬼
You have been a toxic jerk since you got here.
我怎么知道这些不是你编造的
How do I know you're not just spinning this
为了让我不知道你真正的行动
to get me off the scent of what you're actually up to?
因为那个讨厌鬼就是个谎言
Because that jerk was a lie.
这个身份是为了让凯特科的人
An identity I put on to keep everyone at CatCo
不想去了解我
from wanting to get to know me.
-那倒是起作用了  -这难受死我了
- Well, it worked. - And it killed me.
每次我对你无礼
Every time I was rude to you,
每次我对自己的所作所为撒谎
every time I lied about what I've really been up to.
既然你知道了
Now that you know,
至少我可以跟你说实话
at least I can be honest with you.
或许至少你能原谅我
At least maybe you can forgive me.
我觉得这不可能
I don't think that's gonna happen.
我不怪你
I don't blame you.
换我也会讨厌我自己
I'd hate me too.
给你冷遇
Giving you the cold shoulder.
为了接近安德里亚而变得超级好胜
Being hypercompetitive in order to get closer to Andrea.
批评你的写作
Criticizing your writing,
而没有告诉你我的真实想法
instead of telling you what I really thought.
你是说我的作品不是真的"无病呻吟"
You mean my work's not really "Sentimental tripe"?
你的新闻内容坦诚  用语精辟
Your articles are honest and smart.
我永远写不出你那样的文章
I could never write the way you write.
你得过两次普利策奖
You have two Pulitzers.
不是因为写作
It's not from the writing.
是因为报道内容
It's from the story.
我有技巧  你有艺术
I have craft, you have art.
现在向我保证你会放手
Now promise me you'll let this go.
如果你被卷入这件事  我永远不会原谅自己
I'd never forgive myself if you got wrapped up in this.
你不用担心我
You don't have to worry about me.
我能照顾自己
I can take care of myself.
我丝毫不怀疑
I don't doubt that you can
你能做好任何你想做的事
take care of everything you set your mind to.
加尔文镇公报
加尔文镇监狱: 过度拥挤与过重刑罚
不敢相信你回来了
Can't believe you came back.
而且买下了报纸
That you bought the paper.
我还能说什么
What can I say?
我喜欢挑战
I like a challenge.
谁知道  或许你和我可以一起修复这个小镇
Who knows, maybe you and I could fix this town together.
对了
By the way,
你知道怎么用照相机吗
you know how to work a camera?
是用手机拍照吗
Like, on my phone?
不  不是手机拍照
No, not like on your phone.
是用真正的相机
Like a real one.
我爸爸给了我这台相机
My dad gave me this camera.
现在它是你的了
And now it's yours.
谢谢  头儿
Thanks, Chief.
别叫我头儿
Don't call me chief.
叫我吉米
It's Jimmy.
我在哪里
Where am I?
这里不是幻影区
This is not the Phantom Zone.
现在你已经意识到你不能穿过这些墙了
By now you've realized you can't phase through these walls.
但不要觉得这是个监狱
But don't think of this as a prison.
我不是你的敌人
I'm not your enemy.
事实上  我认为我们可以互相帮助
In fact, I think we can help each other.